<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pranavgade20.github.io/kde-blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pranavgade20.github.io/kde-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-15T20:31:42+05:30</updated><id>https://pranavgade20.github.io/kde-blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Pranav Gade</title><subtitle>A blog to recieve my random ramblings :P</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Season Of KDE 2021</title><link href="https://pranavgade20.github.io/kde-blog/jekyll/update/2021/01/15/season-of-kde-2021.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Season Of KDE 2021" /><published>2021-01-15T19:49:42+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-15T19:49:42+05:30</updated><id>https://pranavgade20.github.io/kde-blog/jekyll/update/2021/01/15/season-of-kde-2021</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pranavgade20.github.io/kde-blog/jekyll/update/2021/01/15/season-of-kde-2021.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello, KDE!
I’m Pranav, a first year bachelor’s student from India. Although I have worked on KDE projects previously during Google Code-in 2018, I had to take a break for university enterance exams. However, now that I am an uni student, I hope to start contributing more and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this SoK, I will be working on adding video annotation support to marK, and Caio Jordão Carvalho will be mentoring me. Although marK only supports text and image annotation at the moment, Jean(a fellow SoK participant) and I will add video and audio annotation support respectively, and I’m looking forward to working with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember talking to Caio about this project, when we met during the Google Code-in 2018 Prize trip, and I thought it was really cool. So, needless to say, I am excited to work on it. I will be progress updates as I work on the project. Until then, happy coding!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Hello, KDE! I’m Pranav, a first year bachelor’s student from India. Although I have worked on KDE projects previously during Google Code-in 2018, I had to take a break for university enterance exams. However, now that I am an uni student, I hope to start contributing more and more.</summary></entry></feed>